Guide to the Gay and Lesbian Pulp Fiction Collection 1955-1988 MSS 116 MSS.116
Fales Library and Special Collections
Gay and Lesbian Pulp Fiction Collection
1955-1988
Fales Library and Special Collections
Bolerium Books
MSS.116
66 Linear Feet (44 boxes)
American queer culture saw some of its earliest mass expression in the pulp fiction market starting around the end of World War II. The collection includes a substantial sampling of the gay pulp fiction genre from the 1950's to the 1980's.
Provenance
Acquired through purchase from Bolerium Books, San Francisco in August 2001.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Historical Note
American queer culture saw some of its earliest mass expression in the pulp fiction market starting around the end of World War II, and though sometimes called "masturbation" books they included some more refined literary expressions with such works as: Flora Fletcher's 'Whisper of Love' (1955); and Andre Tellier's 'Twilight Men' (1957). In the 1940's, the lesbian pulp novels were more prevalent, but by the 1950's the genre saw an increase in gay male pulp novels. To avoid the law, publishers would often change their names and addresses, and writers wrote under pseudonyms. However, the books in the genre dealt with social and political issues along with issues around sexual orientation and erotic expression presenting these subjects in a unique historical perspective. Several prominent gay and lesbian writers worked in the pulp fiction market, among these are Ann Bannon (The Marriage, 1960), Phil Andros (The Greek Way, 1972), and Jane Rule (Against the Season, 1975).
Sources:
"Lesbian & Gay Pulp Fiction Collection A Major Asset to the Archives." Archeion. Volume 2, #2. 2002, June. The Stonewall Library and Archives, Ft Lauderdale Fla. [Online: http://www.stonewall-library.org/Archives/news/Archeion/June2002.htm: 2002, Sept. 29].
Scope and Content Note
The Gay and Lesbian Pulp Fiction Collection is a part of the general special collections at the Fales Library, New York University. The Fales Library is the primary special collections division of the NYU libraries, housing over 200,000 volumes of English and American literature from 1700 to the present. Strengths of the collection include the development of the English and American novel, with an emphasis on the Gothic and the Victorian novel.
The Fales Library's collection of Gay and Lesbian pulp fiction spans four decades (1950s-1980s), and includes the works of several prominent gay and lesbian writers. Among these are Ann Bannon (The Marriage, 1960), Phil Andros (The Greek Way, 1972), and Jane Rule (Against The Season, 1975). The collection also includes titles from a very early period in American queer culture. Flora Fletcher's Whisper of Love (1955) and Andre Tellier's Twilight Men (1957) are two examples of the preliminary steps that America's gay and lesbian writers took in giving literary expression to "the love that dare not speak its name."
The list of publishing houses represented within the Fales collection includes Avon, Bantam, Bathhouse, Blueboy, Eros Goldstripe, Gay Parisian Press, Greenleaf, Lambda, Phenix, Spade Classics, Star Distributors, Surrey, and Traveler's Companion. This collection also includes some foreign publications.
As far as content goes, the Fales collection of gay and lesbian pulp fiction is rather extraordinary. The novels are set in a vast range of geographical areas and historical periods. Many narratives take place in diverse regions of the United States: the Eastern Seaboard, Deep South, Midwest, Texas-Mexico border, and West Coast. Others are set as far away as the oil fields of apartheid South Africa, villas of ancient Greece, Nazi work camps of Eastern Europe, and massage parlors of London. They depict the gay and lesbian lifestyles and/or experiences of ranchers, bikers, businessmen, college students, housewives, soldiers, policemen, movie stars, truck drivers, artists, criminals, teachers, prostitutes and hustlers, as well as a plethora of other actual occupations.
Authors in this collection do more than simply describe the regional specificities and landmarks of a particular locale. They also include vivid accounts of the social, political, and economic circumstances of a specific community. What is it like to live as a black man who desires other men in apartheid South Africa? What sorts of erotic and social-political bonds may exist between a Native American Indian and the white man attracted to him? What fantasies do gays and lesbians have about rape, incest, criminality, and other so-called "aberrations" of social norms? What limited role(s) do women play in gay and lesbian pulps novels of this period? These are just a few examples of the political issues explored by our writers. The authors also grapple with contemporary issues such as crime (including hate crimes), racism, homophobia and misogyny, fascism, as well as the personal/professional opportunities available to gays and lesbians in the second half of the 20th century.
SERIES DESCRIPTION
The Gay and Lesbian Pulp Fiction collection at Fales came to us in three shipments, and we processed each shipment as a separate accretion. The first accretion consists of thirty-three boxes; these boxes are labeled as 1-33. The second accretion consists of five boxes; these boxes are labeled as 34-38. The third accretion consists of seven boxes; these boxes are labeled as 38-44.
Within each accretion, the gay and lesbian pulp fiction is organized alphabetically, by series title. For example, the first box in the first accretion contains novels published under the following series names: "Academy Press," "Adams Gay Reader," "Adonis Classic," "Adults Only," and "Adult Books." The first box in the second accretion contains novels published under the following series names: "Ace," "Adam's Gay Reader," "Adonis Classic," "Ballantine," "Blueboy," "Charter," "Combat," "Corgi," and "Driveshaft." In short, one will need to examine each of the three accretions in order to locate all of the titles belonging to a particular series. Within each separate accretion, the novels are first organized alphabetically, then chronologically, according to series number.
In the event that a novel does not belong to a particular series, the book is then organized by its title. For example, Robert Guy's Boy For Hire can be found in Box 6, appearing alphabetically after "Boudoir Classics 0001," and before "Brandon 933."
Arrangement
Books are arranged alphabetically by the publisher's series name (if none by title) and then by title.
The files are grouped into 3 sets of accretions. Each accretion begins a new alphabet.
Missing Title
First Accretion
Second Accretion
Third Accretion
Related Material at the Fales Library and Special Collections
Levy Dime Novel Collectiom (MSS.028)
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Gay erotic literature.; Homosexuality in literature.; Paperbacks.; American fiction -- 20th century.; Lesbians |x Fiction.; Books.; Gay men's writings, American.; Lesbians' writings, American.; Pulp literature.; Lesbians in literature.; Gay men in literature.; Gay men |v Fiction.; Bannon, Ann; Cockran, Bob; Cummings, Rich; Caldwell, Clay; Dean, Douglas, 1920-; Evans, Jack; Dale, Dick; Davidson, Chris; Greene, Jay; Griffon, David; Everts, Tag; Graeme, Roland; Maltese, William; Wilson, George; West, Samuel; Tulane, Rick; Thomas, Aaron; Tellier, André, 1902-; Stuart, Chad; Stroth, Dick; Smith, Art; Savage, Lon; Sawyers, Rod; Rogers, Lance; Rule, Jane; Montague, Murray; Pepper, Peter, 1899-; Michaels, Ward; Miller, Marcus; Maggie, John; McClain, Burt; Kincaid, Jeff; Lamb, Sebastian; Harrington, Len; Hughes, Peter Tuesday; Gronowski, Paul; Hall, Marnie
- First Accretion
  - Academy Press 9670. Preston, Harry: Confessions of a Closet Queen. (Academy Press), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061124 9
  - Adams Gay Reader 103. Starr, Elihu: The Rearing of Lazarus. (Surey), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adams Gay Reader 115. Kincaid, Jeff: Hot Shorts. (Surey), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adonis Classic 102. Andros, Phil: The Greek Way. (Greenleaf), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Adonis Classic 126. McLean, Curt: Brother Gay. (Greenleaf), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adonis Classic 142. Love, F.W.: Hard and Hungry. (Greenleaf), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adonis Classic 186. Love, F.W.: Locker Room Stud. (Greenleaf), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adults Only. Bannis, Lester: The Cruiser. (w.l), undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adults Only. Tarme, Howard: Red. (w.l), undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adult Book 403. Davidson, Chris: Caves of Iron. (Adult Books), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adult Books 430. James, Allan: Belle of the Boat. (Adult Books), 1967) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adult Books 431. Harrington, Len: His Kind of Love. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adult Books 432. Brown, L.J.: The Queens Are In the Parlor. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Adult Books 433. Davidson, Chris: Buffy and the Holy Quest. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Adult Books 434. Branch, Chris: A Few Good Men. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Adult Books 435. Miller, Marcus: Gay Twins. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Adult Books 437. Vickery, Jay: Gay Dreams. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Adult Books 440. Thomas, Aaron: Charlie Darling. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Adult Books 441. Branch, Carl: All Shades of Gay. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Adult Books 443. Thomas, Aaron: Gay Orgy. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Adult Books 445. Lester, Lance: Gay Vista. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Adult Books 446. North, Gene: Good-Bye, Gay Love. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Adult Books 447. Dale, Dick: Call Boy. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Adult Books 448. Miller, Marcus: Captive In Lavender. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Adult Books 449. Calvano, Tony: Under Fire Fags. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Adult Books 451. Lynn, David: Bull Nuts. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Adult Books 452. Dale, Dick: Gay Paragon. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Adult Books 453. Vickery, Jay: Brandon's Boy. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Adult Books 454. Davidson, Chris: Buffy Rides Again. (Adult Books), 1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - All Star Books 46. Barnes, Gregory: Homo Alley. (All Star), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061125 6
  - All Star Books 88. Benton, Riley: The Dungaree Jungle. (All Star), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - All Star Books 96. Masters, Simon: The Gay Savages. (All Star), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Avon 54 Dowd, Harrison: The Night Air. (Avon), 1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Avon 380-17251-175. Merrick, Gordon: Forth Into Light. (Avon), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Avon 0-380-38992-4-225. Merrick, Gordon: The Quirk. (Avon), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Avon 0-380-47647-9-250. Case, Ensan: Wing Men. (Avon), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Avon 0-380-79616-3-295. Reinhart, Robert: A History of Shadows. (Avon), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Avon 0-380-75820-2-295. Virga, Vincent: Gaywyck. (Avon), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Avon 0-380-76547-0-275. Snyder, William: Tory's. (Avon), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Avon 0-380-77867-X-295. Merrick, Gordon: Now Let's Talk About Music. (Avon), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Avon 0-380-80895-1-350. Virga, Vincent: A Comfortable Corner. (Avon), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Avon 0-380-82230-X-250. Hamilton, Mark: My Brother's Image. (Avon), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Backdoor Library 1003. Dillon, Allan: Hard and Heated. (Star Distributors), undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Backdoor Library 1008 Halman, Scott: Cock Hungry Creamers. (Star Distributors), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bantam 553-05402-095. Chopping, Richard: The Ring. (Bantam), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bantam 553-07874-150. Anonymous: Us. (Bantam), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Barclay House Homophile Fiction 7023. Otto, Grant: Making the Team. (Barclay House), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061126 4
  - Barclay House Homophile Fiction 7034. Kaplan, George: Homo 69.. (Barclay House), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Barclay House Homophile Fiction 7054. Maggie, John: The Honey Horn. (Barclay House), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bark Books. Midcon, Seymour: The Male Erection. (Bark Books), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bathhouse Books. Nita, Brian: Stick Shift. (Bathhouse), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bathhouse Books. Cory, John: Learning the Hard Way. (Bathhouse), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Beacon B280. Norday, Michael: Warped.. (Beacon), 1955) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Beacon B282. Kent, Justin: Mavis. (Beacon), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Beacon B300. Dean, Ralph: Lingerie LTD. (Beacon), 1960 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Beacon B390. Martin, Della: Twilight Girl. (Beacon), 1961 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Beacon B854F. Maxwell, Malcolm: The Other Side of Love. (Beacon Signal), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Beacon Signal B586F. Simon, George: The Third Lust. (Beacon), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Beacon Signal B589F. Roberts, Herb: Love In the Shadows. (Beacon), 19 63 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Beacon Signal B602F. Aldon, Arthur: She Who Strays. (Beacon), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Beacon Signal B731X. Williams, A.P.: Tutor From Lesbos. (Beacon), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Beacon Signal B771X. Pruett, Herbert: The Abnormal Ones. (Beacon), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Beacon Signal B791X. Salem, Randy: Baby Face. (Beacon), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Berkeley Books G245. Mark, Edwina: The Odd Ones. (Berkeley Publishing), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Big Boy Series 104. Trix, Bobby: Pleasure Boy Sucker. (Big Boy), undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Blue boy Library 80000. Montague, Murray: Security Risk. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Blue boy Library 80003. Lamb, Sebastian: The Secret Meeting. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Blue boy Library 80004. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: The Wisteria Club. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Blue boy Library 80005. Lamb, Sebastian: Brothers. (Blue boy), 1976) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Blue boy Library 80007. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: The Bright Young Men. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Blue boy Library 80011. McClain, Burt: Gunfighter's Glory. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061127 2
  - Blue boy Library 80015. Portland, Franklin: Pipeline. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Blue boy Library 80016. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: Three Got Away. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Blue boy Library 80019. Harper, Sydney: Two, The Hard Way. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Blue boy Library 80021. Montague, Murray: My Man David. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Blue boy Library 80022. Stone, Jack: The Running Man. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Blue boy Library 80023. Hardy, Tom: Adventures of a High School Hunk. (Blue boy), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Blue boy Library 80025. Montague, Murray: The Trouble With Peter. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Blue boy Library 80026. Lamb, Sebastian: The Two Faces of Janus. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Blue boy Library 80028. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: The Eyes of the Basilisk. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Blue boy Library 80029.Gronowski, Paul: The Caribbean Connection. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Blue boy Library 80031. Martin, Moore: To Dare to be Different. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Blue boy Library 80032. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: The Daemon. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Blue boy Library 80034. Gronowski, Paul: Behind the Badge. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Blue boy Library 80035. Lamb, Sebastian: The Slasher. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Blue boy Library 80036. Montague, Murray: Yesterday's Closet. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Blue boy Library 80037. MacRoy, John: Brother of the Wind. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Blue boy Library 80038. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: Garden of Cruel Delights. (Blueboy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Blue boy Library 80039. McBride, Scott: The Pride and the Power. (Blueboy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Blue boy Library 80041. Hastings, Banner: The Heisters. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Blue boy Library 80042. Bartrand, Franklin: Pharoah's Champion. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Blue boy Library 80050. Hastings, Banner: Blackmailed. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Blue boy Library 80057. Montague, Murray: The Other Side of Love. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Blue boy Library 80058. McClain, Burt: Shootout in Cheyenne. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061128 0
  - Blue boy Library 80059. Lang, Raymond R: The Secret of the Phallic Stone. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Blue boy Library 80060. Gronowski, Paul: Master of Men. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Blue boy Library 80061. Lamb, Sebastian: King of Hearts. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Blue boy Library 80062. Lang, Raymond C: In The Hole. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Blue boy Library 80063. McBride, Scott: Pride, Integrity, Gay. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Blue boy Library 80065. Stone, Jack: The Mystery of Toomey's Island. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Blue boy Library 80070. Gronowski, Paul: The Isabel Conspiracy, Book I. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Blue boy Library 80071. Gronowski, Paul: The Isabel Conspiracy, Book II. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Blue boy Library 80072. McClain, Burt: Cal Jardine. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Blue boy Library 80073. Savage, Lon: Knave of Diamonds. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Blue boy Library 80074. LaFong, Lance: Iron Men. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Blue boy Library 80081. Pulanski, Gary: My Cousin...My Lover. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Blue boy Library 80082. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: Phallic Worshippers. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Blue boy Library 80083. Savage, Lon: Ace of Spades. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Blue boy Library 80084. McClain, Burt: Cal Jardine, Book II. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Blue boy Library 80085. Ironstone, John: Orphan. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Blue boy Library 80086. Gronowski, Paul: To Kill A King. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Blue boy Library 80088. Williams, Randy: Stage Stud. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Blue boy Library 80089. Stuart, Chad: The Siegfried Mating. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Blue boy Library 80090. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: The Monte Carlo Caper. (Blue boy), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Blue boy Library BB125. Stone, Jack: The Bikers. (Blue boy), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Boudior Classics 1. Biship, George: Lesbian Love. (Tempo Publishing), 1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061129 8
  - Boy For Hire. Guy, Robert, A. (w.l), undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Brandon 933. Colson, Frederick: The Devil Is Gay. (Brandon), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Brandon 1015. O'Connor, L.R.: The Sexual Underworld. (Brandon), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Brandon 2050. Carmichael, K.C.: The Snake and the Womb. (Brandon), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Brandon 2055. Maggie, John: Go Down In the Valley. (Brandon), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Brandon 3036. Spatari, William Charles: Weekend Homo. (Brandon), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Brandon 3044. Evans, Gene: Murder On Queer Street. (Brandon), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Brandon 3065. Michaels, Phil: The Naive Homosexual. (Brandon), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Brandon 3073. Sawyers, Rod: The Flesh Mast. (Brandon), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Brandon 6089. Carter, Mike: New Meat. (Brandon), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Brandon 6096. Milton, Jack: Queens of the Road. (Brandon), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Brandon 6108. Martin, Jonathan: Soldiers of Sodom. (Brandon), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Brentwood Crime Adventure Series 12. Brent, Lynton Wright: Sir Gay. (Brentwood), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Buddy Books 150. Anonymous: Hot Surfer Buns. (Buddy), 1981 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - CAJ (Cajon). Poindexter, Felix: Stud Ranch (CAJ), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cameo Library 166. Ballard, Jess: Mostly Male. (Cameo), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Cameo Library 8004. Evans, Gene: Homo Hunt. (Cameo), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Cameo Library 928042. Stein, Jock: The Gay Love Letters. (Cameo), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Club Series 103. Reese, Stan: The Lucky Pick-Up. (Star Distributors), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Club Series 105. Slade, Rick: Stud Sucker. (Star Distributors), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Club Series 108. Whitne, Flinn: Rich Man's Sex Toys. (Star Distributors), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Club Series 119. Scander, Rudy: The Star's Young Boyfriend. (Star Distributors), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Club Series 122. Salter, Harold: Humping Hitchhiker. (Star Distributors), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Club Series 128. Marcus, James: Rough Reamers. (Star Distributors), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061130 6
  - Club Series 131. Ferren, George: The Butt Branders. (Star Distributors), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Club Series 132. Evans, Jack: Ten Inches to Paradise. (Star Distributors), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Club Series 134. Ferren, George: Dude Ranch Suckers. (Star Distributors), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Club Series 135. Marcus, James: The Giant Lover. (Star Distributors), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Combat Books 101. Anonymous: Nazi Sadist. (Combat), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Companion Book 546. Lester, Lance: Cruising Horny Corners. (Companion), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Companion Book 547. Dale, Dick: Gay On the Range. (Companion), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Companion Book 548. Miller, Marcus: Carry On, Charlie. (Companion), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Companion Book 551. Thomas, Aaron: The Greek Affair. (Companion), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Companion Book 552. Dale, Dick: Gay But Not Happy. (Companion), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Companion Book 554. Miller, Marcus: The Gay Swap. (Companion), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Companion Book 555. Fair, Alan: Villa of Queens. (Companion), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Companion Book 557. Dale, Dick: Four-Way Gay. (Companion), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Companion Book 558. Miller, Marcus: The Mother Truckers. (Companion), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Companion Book 559. Fair, Alan: The Boys In Olive Drag. (Companion), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Companion Book 560. Harrington, Len: We Three Queens. (Companion), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Companion Book 562. Thomas, Aaron: Gay Traders. (Companion), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Companion Book 563. Fair, Alan: A Man's Affair. (Companion), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Cruiser Classic 102. Russell, Thomas: San Francisco Slave-Boy. (Cruiser), undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Dell 0.440.98266.9. Hall, Lynn: Sticks and Stones. (Dell), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Domino Books 72-905. Adlon, Arthur: Speak It In Whispers. (Domino), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Domino Books 72-938. Fields, Vin: Who Seek In Shadow. (Domino), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Domino Books 72-951. Sharon, Sylvia: The Agony of Desire. (Domino), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Drive Shaft Library 101. Taylor, Rick: Horny Hijackers. (Arena Publications), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Drive Shaft Library 102. Woodward, Mike: Superstar Stud. (Arena Publications), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Drive Shaft Library 105. Woodward, Mike: Hard Pecker. (Arena Publications), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 27)